

- 012-399 5766
- 22120158@imail.sunway.edu.my
- https://xuxuannn.github.io/
- Atmosfera Condominium, Puchong

Skill

Time Management **Teamwork** Research Communication

Technical skills:

Java - basic

C++ - basic

HTML - advanced

CSS - advanced

PHP - intermediate

MySQL - advanced

JavaScript - intermediate

Software:

MS Office, VS Code, Android Studio, Figma, XAMPP, Apache Netbean.

Extra-Curricular Activities

Sunway Diploma Student Council Sunway Leo Club Sunway Music Society

Language

Mandarin - advanced **English - intermediate** Malay - intermediate Hokkien - basic Tech Chew - basic

LIM HAN XUAN

IT INTERNSHIP

Profile

As a dedicated and motivated IT student, I possess a solid IT foundation and diverse skills. I am passionate about translating theoretical knowledge into practical solutions, eagerly utilizing my programming skills and collaborative spirit throughout my internship. My goal is to combine classroom learning with practical experience, hoping to learn new knowledge throughout the internship. I look forward to the work and tasks ahead.

Education

April 2023 - Present

Diploma in Information Technology

SUNWAY COLLEGE

CGPA 2.85

2018 - 2023

SMK DATUK HAJI ABDUL KADIR

SPM 1B+ 2B 5C+ 1E

Work Experience

Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

SK Success Management

Data entry for customer information using MS excel.

Nov 2022 - Dec 2022

Rina Property SDN BHD

Data entry for sales and issue invoice in Accounting system (SQL).

References

Chik Soon Wai

Lecturer

Phone: 016-318 2021

Email: soonwaic@sunway.edu.my

Selina Khoo

TECH REALTORS PROPERTIES SDN BHD

ASSOCIATE DIRECTOR Phone: 012-588 5796

Email: selina.techpng@gmail.com